User Experience/UI Designer

139-66 86th Avenue Briarwood, NY (347)262-4892 angelipen@gmail.com

GOAL

Join a team that specializes in application development and research. Contribute my art and design strenghths toward a centralized goal in a challenging environment where as to further enhance my knowledge and understanding of user habits and behavior.

SKILLS

Adobe XD GitHub SCRUM Behavioral Psycology Photoshop Wireframing InVision Branding

Illustrator Prototyping Microsoft

EXPERIENCE

Massachusetts Institute of Technoloy Center for Brains, Minds, and Machines 05.2018 Freelance UX/UI Designer

Lead user interface designer for neural network community website. Led application research, performed a needs analysis and coordinated with software engineering team via use of an agile development platform.

Uber/ Lyft 10.2016 - Present Driver

Safetly transport passangers to their destinations while following NYC Traffic regulations

Empathize with passangers under stress

4.96 Rating for Excellent Service & Great Conversation

Client Care Coordinator Allen Home Care Agency

09.2013 - 06.2016

Build relationships with patients and home health aides Collaborate with team members to meet daily/ weekly goals Communicate efficiently with contract, nurses, and other departments

Complete daily reports to ensure work is completed Address patient/ HHA issues with empathy and provide possible solutions with high priority

CERTIFICATIONS

CUNY Techworks Certification in User Experience Design 03.2018 - 06.2018

15 week Intensive course lead by 3 top User Experience Designers where design thinking, visual design, and product management were the main focus.

Global Traditional Wing Chun Kung Fu Association Level 5 Brown Sash

Four years of consistant training and discipline in a Kung Fu Academy. Indulging in Martial Arts has added soft skills in self awareness, social interaction, empathy, and conflict resolution.

EDUCATION

Kingsborough Community College

09.2017 - In Progress

Computer Information Systems

Art & Design High School

09.2006 - 06.2010

Architecture Advanced Regents Diploma